yearbookyourself.com 2009-03-04

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Yearbook Yourself website (the “Website”).  Because your privacy is important to us, The Taubman Company LLC and each shopping center managed by The Taubman Company LLC participating in this Website has provided the following notice explaining our privacy and information practices for this Website to you.  

This statement outlines our privacy policy (our "Policy"). When you use the Website or provide information to us (including by completing an entry, registration or other form), you agree to the terms of this Policy. We may make changes to this Policy, without notice to you, from time to time and any such changes will become effective 7 days after being posted. You are responsible for checking periodically for changes.  By accessing the Website, you indicate your agreement to and acceptance of the terms of this Policy, and consent to the collection, retention and use of your personally identifiable information consistent with this Policy, as amended from time to time.  If you are visiting our Website from outside the United States, there may be special rules or limitations on your use of this Web site. 

## What type of information do we collect?

We may collect certain limited information about you when you visit the Website.  Such information might consist of your name, if you provide it, e-mail address and computer identification.

## How do we collect the information?

The Website may use cookies to collect information about your computer in order to facilitate your use of the Website.  For example, when you visit the Website, cookies allow us to recognize you, and then when you return to our website, they allow us to direct you to your Homeroom page on the Website.  Cookies do not allow us to personally identify you, but help us improve the quality of your visit to the Website.  We also collect information that you provide to us when sign up for an email alert, such information might consist of your name, if you provide it, e-mail address and computer identification. 

## How do we use the information you provide us?

We will use the information that you provide us only to facilitate your use of the Website and email alert.  We will only save your information for a one-time email alert (other than cookies), and we will not transfer or sell information about you to any third parties except to a business partner which operates the Website.  If we should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company while we still have any personally identifiable information collected through this Website, or if we should decide to buy, sell or reorganize some part or all of our business, we may be required to disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers or receive personal information from sellers. 

Although we will protect your privacy on the Website as described in this Policy, you should keep in mind that if you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information may be accessible to others. This is also true if anyone else has access to your personal computer, such as an employer or family member. However, if you link to a third party website from the Website, any information you reveal on that website is not subject to this Policy. You should consult the privacy policies of each website you visit.

We may be required to disclose your personal information such as your name, if you provide it, e-mail address and computer identification if we believe it is necessary to comply with legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, etc.), or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit; is otherwise necessary to protect our rights or property; or is necessary to protect the interests of other users of the Website. 

## How do we protect kids' privacy?

We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.  We also do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13, or knowingly allow such persons to register.  If you are under 13, you should not attempt to register for the Website or send information about yourself to us. 

If we become aware that a user of the Website is under the age of 13 and is without verifiable parental consent, we will remove any personally identifiable information about that person from our files.

## What about links to other websites and services?

The Website may contain links to other websites that we do not control; those websites have their own policies and procedures regarding privacy. We recommend that you review those policies before entering those websites, as we have no responsibility for any linked websites. We simply provide those links for your convenience.

## **International visitors consent to this Policy too**

Privacy laws differ across the globe.  If it is necessary for the purposes for which you have shared personal information with us for us to share your information within our global operations, we will do so consistent with this Policy.

This site is hosted in the United States and is intended for United States visitors.  If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from United States law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States and by providing your personal data you consent to that transfer.  When you provide personal data to us or our service providers or vendors, you consent to the processing of your data in the United States as the site is operated in the United States.

**

Policy Effective Date

**

 _:   July _25_, 2008.  _
